<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movies</string>
    <string name="posters_link">Постеры предоставлены \n https://www.movieposters.com/collections/franchise-pixar</string>
    <string name="menu">Меню</string>
    <string name="favorite">Избранное</string>
    <string name="watch_later">Посмотреть позже</string>
    <string name="selections">Подборки</string>
    <string name="settings">Настройки</string>
    <string name="page_title">movies</string>

    //не вышло, но пытался
    <string name="movie_1">Prey</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_1">The origin story of the Predator in the world of the Comanche Nation 300 years ago. Naru, a skilled warrior, fights to protect her tribe against one of the first highly-evolved Predators to land on Earth.</string>
    <string name="movie_2">Bullet Train</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_2">Five assassins aboard a fast moving bullet train find out their missions have something in common.</string>
    <string name="movie_3">Thirteen Lives</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_3">A rescue mission is assembled in Thailand where a group of young boys and their soccer coach are trapped in a system of underground caves that are flooding.</string>
    <string name="movie_4">Purple Hearts</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_4">In spite of their many differences, Cassie, a struggling singer-songwriter, and Luke, a troubled Marine, agree to marry solely for military benefits. But when tragedy strikes, the line between real and pretend begins to blur.</string>
    <string name="movie_5">Nope</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_5">The residents of a lonely gulch in inland California bear witness to an uncanny and chilling discovery.</string>
    <string name="movie_6">The Gray Man</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_6">When the CIA\'s most skilled operative-whose true identity is known to none-accidentally uncovers dark agency secrets, a psychopathic former colleague puts a bounty on his head, setting off a global manhunt by international assassins.</string>
    <string name="movie_7">Elvis</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_7">The life of American music icon Elvis Presley, from his childhood to becoming a rock and movie star in the 1950s while maintaining a complex relationship with his manager, Colonel Tom Parker.</string>
    <string name="movie_8">Day Shift</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_8">A hard-working, blue-collar dad who just wants to provide a good life for his quick-witted 8-year-old daughter. His mundane San Fernando Valley pool cleaning job is a front for his real source of income: hunting and killing vampires.</string>
    <string name="movie_9">Uncharted</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_9">Street-smart Nathan Drake is recruited by seasoned treasure hunter Victor "Sully" Sullivan to recover a fortune amassed by Ferdinand Magellan, and lost 500 years ago by the House of Moncada.</string>
    <string name="movie_10">Lightyear</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_10">While spending years attempting to return home, marooned Space Ranger Buzz Lightyear encounters an army of ruthless robots commanded by Zurg who are attempting to steal his fuel source.</string>
</resources>